Narrator: 1
F: The research looked into the effect of noise pollution on birds in the area.
Narrator: 2
F: The extract was taken from a recent research paper.
Narrator: 3
M: Demand for electric cars is expected to increase over the next decade.
Narrator: 4
F: That factory produced chocolate bars until it closed down last year.
Narrator: 5
M: The firm lost the contract to a large multinational.
Narrator: 6
F: The senior researcher told us to record our observations carefully.
Narrator: 7
M: The building work will go ahead despite protests from local residents.
Narrator: 8
F: What’s the latest update on the fires in Australia?
Narrator: 9
M: We have a difficult relationship because his opinions tend to conflict with mine.
Narrator: 10
F: The researchers surveyed the attitudes of 3,000 university students.